indigoclothing.com 2007-11-03

# Privacy Policy | Indigo Clothing

At Indigo Clothing Ltd. we are committed to protecting your privacy. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

**Controllers of personal information**

Any personal information provided or to be gathered by Indigo Clothing is controlled primarily by Indigo Clothing Ltd.

**What information do we collect and how is it used?**

When you place an order or request a quote we need to know your name, e-mail address, delivery address, credit or debit card number and expiry date. This information allows us to process and fulfil your orders.

Your telephone number is also collected in case we need to contact you urgently if there is a problem with your order.

We may also use the order details to occasionally notify you about changes to the website, new services and special offers we think you may find useful. You can opt out by visiting the [newsletter section ](http://www.indigoclothing.com/info_newsletter.shtml)of the website or by contacting us.

We do not sell, trade, rent or otherwise pass your personal details to any third party.

**How is my information protected?  
**  
All transactions on this website are protected by a secure server (SSL). All personal information that you input is encrypted before being sent through the internet.

Also, it is required by the UK Data Protection Legislation that we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given us.

**What are "cookies"?**

Cookies are small packets of information that are stored by your web browser onto your hard drive. We may occasionally store information about your last visit to the website, but no personal information will be stored.

**Your consent**

By using this website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Indigo Clothing Ltd. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.
